<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on This sample size equals one</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on This sample size equals one</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/talks/</guid>
      <description> Resurrecting Ancient Proteins in Python | SciPy 2018   How Jupyter Makes Experimental and Computational Collaborations Easy | JupyterCon 2017   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing your own flavor of Pandas</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/software/pandas-flavor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/software/pandas-flavor/</guid>
      <description>Pandas is Python&amp;rsquo;s DataFrame library. There are many reasons why should be using DataFrame&amp;rsquo;s in your data science workflow, but I&amp;rsquo;ll have to leave that for another post. Here, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to tailor Pandas to your business, research, or personal workflow using Pandas&amp;rsquo; extension API.
In versions 0.24.x, Pandas introduced a new API for extending Pandas. This API handled the boilerplate code for registering custom accessors onto Pandas objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should Jupyter Notebooks go away?</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/jupyter/notebook-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 14:50:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/jupyter/notebook-communication/</guid>
      <description>Recently, there has been a lot of discussion on whether the hype around Jupyter Notebooks is deserved.
Critics say that Notebooks are bad for software development. They actually encourage a lot of bad practices and confuse people who are learning to program. This is a fair criticism, and I mostly agree. (I recommend watching the talk, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t like notebooks.&amp;rdquo; to hear some common criticisms).
The dominant counter argument I hear is&amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupyter Team Meeting 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/jupyter/jupyter-team-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 11:30:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/jupyter/jupyter-team-meeting/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;If you want to go fast, go alone. If you want to go far, go together.&amp;rdquo;
 A few weeks ago, I had the opportunity to join many members of the Project Jupyter&amp;rsquo;s core development team in Washington DC for our annual team meeting. A huge thank you to Dr. Lorena Barba for hosting our team at George Washington University for the week.
This was an incredible experience.
I counted ~20 core contributors representing 9 different countries in the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, world.</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/other/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 17:36:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/other/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Finally starting a blog. Thank you to Leticia Portella and Saul Shanabrook for pushing to make it happened.
I&amp;rsquo;m planning to use this site to share three major types of content.
 I&amp;rsquo;ll announce software that I&amp;rsquo;ve published or review software someone else published.
 I&amp;rsquo;ll highlight things I come across in basic science and research domains. Since my background is in science, I&amp;rsquo;ll use this blog to stay connected to that community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>