<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 14:50:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Should Jupyter Notebooks go away?</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/jupyter/notebook-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 14:50:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/jupyter/notebook-communication/</guid>
      <description>Recently, there has been a lot of discussion on whether the hype around Jupyter Notebooks is deserved.
Critics say that Notebooks are not actually good for software development. In fact, they actually encourage bad software engineering/development practices. This is a fair criticism, and I actually agree. (I recommend watching the talk, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t like notebooks.&amp;rdquo; to hear some common criticisms).
The dominant counter argument I hear is&amp;ndash;
 The interactivity offered by Notebooks is a &amp;ldquo;net win&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupyter Team Meeting 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/jupyter/jupyter-team-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 11:30:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/jupyter/jupyter-team-meeting/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;If you want to go fast, go alone. If you want to go far, go together.&amp;rdquo;
 A few weeks ago, I had the opportunity to join many members of the Project Jupyter&amp;rsquo;s core development team in Washington DC for our annual team meeting. A huge thank you to Dr. Lorena Barba for hosting our team at George Washington University for the week.
This was an incredible experience.
I counted ~20 core contributors representing 9 different countries in the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, world.</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/other/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 17:36:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/other/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Finally starting a blog. Thank you to Letitia Portella and Saul Shanabrook for pushing to make it happened.
I&amp;rsquo;m planning to use this site to share three major types of content.
 I&amp;rsquo;ll announce software that I&amp;rsquo;ve published or review software someone else published.
 I&amp;rsquo;ll highlight things I come across in basic science and research domains. Since my background is in science, I&amp;rsquo;ll use this blog to stay connected to that community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>